Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
[intriguing music playing]
[music swells. trails off]
[bell dings]
[contestant 1 on TV]
Public transportation. 400.
[host] The nicer buses
within South Korean cities…
- …are scenes of that Belgian city. Kyle.
- [contestant 2] A metro station?
- [host] Correct.
- US Rep. & Prez for 800.
[host] Andrew Johnson had been a senator
and representative from this state.
- What is Tennessee?
- [host] Adriana.
- [host] Yes.
[Adriana] US Rep. & Prez. 1.200.
[cell phone ringing]
Hello.
Hello. honey.
Oh. Gracie.
I miss you.
I miss you too.
How was your day?
I had pizza for lunch.
- Oh. that's good. That's your favorite.
- Yeah.
Can I come home?
- Not today.
- Oh…
But I'll come see you tomorrow.
How does that sound?
Yeah. we could take Joey to the park.
He'd love that.
Yeah. fly a kite.
- That'd be nice.
- Yeah.
The owl is in the walls. Gracie.
- Owl is in the walls.
- [orderly] Bedtime. Edward.
- A few more minutes.
- [orderly] No. it's time.
It's okay. We'll talk tomorrow.
[Edward] I'm not a damn child.
- [orderly] Give me the phone. Edward!
- Edward. stop!
[Edward] Let go of it!
- Please.
- [orderly] Don't--
I saw my parents. I saw your father.
I saw the Ritz brothers.
Believe me. they're much funnier dead.
- [Dorothy] I'm taking you to the hospital.
- [Sophia] No.
[Dorothy] Why not? What?
Are you trying to tell me that possibly
there is nothing wrong with you?
No. I feel better just lying here.
The ride in the car
could only make me feel worse.
She's right. Dorothy.
Sometimes just lying motionless
is the best thing a person can do.
That didn't sound right on our honeymoon.
and it doesn't sound right now.
[jarring stinger]
[chilling music playing]
[guttural clicking. growling]
[suspenseful music escalating]
Help me!
Somebody help me!
[TV signal drones]
[intriguing. unsettling
intro music playing]
[music trails off]
[child on tablet]
Put it in your pocket. Someday…
My grandmother gave it to me
when I come to the city.
- So I not be run over.
- No…
Is this supposed to be scary?
It's a classic.
- It's boring.
- Can I play a game?
I don't have any games.
Mom. Grandpa's not sharing.
Dad. please?
Fine. take it.
So. is Pill Reminder Pro a game?
No. don't touch that.
Grandpa uses it to keep track of
all the medicines he needs to stay alive.
Oh. I accidentally deleted it.
Probably for the best.
[man] Don't worry about that. Grandpa.
It's all in the cloud.
I'm gonna fix it for you.
- Thank you. Neil.
- Yeah.
[woman] Everyone. look. We're here.
[flatly] Yippee.
[dispatch] I need a couple units
over at The Manor. please.
Hello there. folks.
How can I help you all?
Hi. Um. my dad's moving in today.
His name's Sam Cooper.
Sam Cooper. Got him right here.
Welcome to The Boroughs.
where you'll have the time of your life.
Ironic slogan
for a place people come to die.
Okay.
["Golden Years" by David Bowie playing]
[funky. glitzy pop music playing]
♪ Golden years ♪
♪ Gold. wah-wah-wah ♪
[grandchild 1] Why is everyone so old?
[woman] Because. honey.
this is a special town just for grown-ups.
♪ Don't let me hear you say
Life's taking you nowhere. angel ♪
Hey.
♪ I'll stick with you. baby
For a thousand years ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna touch you
In these golden years ♪
[woman in red] Hi there!
- Hello!
- [woman] Sorry we're late.
It's no problem.
They pay me the medium bucks to be here.
Aren't you just the cutest thing?
- What's your name?
- Sam.
Mr. Cooper.
Nice to officially meet you.
I'm Kayleigh. your transition manager.
It's my privilege to guide you
through every step of your time here.
I hope it's okay.
but I told the movers to start unloading.
The boxes are so well-labeled.
I guess I shouldn't be surprised.
given you are an engineer.
I was an engineer.
But now I'm a prisoner.
We'd love to get into the house.
[Kayleigh] Everything has been
freshly painted.
We kept the wallpaper.
like your wife requested.
Oh. and the previous owner
left some furniture behind.
so feel free to keep
the pieces that speak to you
and get rid of the rest.
Why don't they want it?
Because they're dead. right?
Grace passed two months ago.
but Edward is a resident at The Manor.
It's a long-term care facility here
for those who require more attention.
- What's wrong with him?
- Ella.
- What? I want to know.
- Mm-mmm.
That's quite the boob-tube.
He likes to fix old TVs.
Oh. isn't that fun?
[Sam] What the hell is that?
[Kayleigh] That is Seraphim.
Every house in The Boroughs has one.
If you ever have an emergency.
or. say. you want to book a tee time.
all you have to do
is call out to Seraphim.
and it will connect you
to one of our 24-7 support team.
Here.
Howdy. Seraphim.
[Seraphim] Well. hey there. Kayleigh.
What can I do
to make your day more enjoyable?
Absolutely not.
- Dad?
- Mr. Cooper.
[woman] What are you doing?
- Mr. Cooper. please don't.
- Don't!
Seraphim is actually hardwired.
I do not need an electronic babysitter!
Mr. Cooper. I understand your frustration.
Do you. now?
[Kayleigh] I know it was your wife
who wanted to move here.
and I was so sorry to hear of her passing.
But I'm not the one
who won't let you out of your contract.
Those things are decided
by the man at the top.
So point me his way.
I've helped a lot of people
through this transition over the years.
And I promise.
if you just open your heart to this place.
you'll find The Boroughs
is not a last chapter.
It's a new beginning.
Wait!
Mr. Cooper!
- [woman] Was that really necessary?
- Yes.
She was just doing her job.
- I will not be spoken to like a child.
- Then stop acting like one!
- Excuse me?
- Maybe we all just take a deep breath.
- I didn't ask you to come.
- Not like you can drive yourself!
Hey!
- Let's all go out to the garage.
- [Sam] Why?
What's in the garage. Neil?
Cool.
What the hell is that?
- It's a golf cart.
- I don't play golf.
It's not just a golf cart. okay?
This is the ICON i40L.
It's got a 48-volt. three-phase.
high-torque motor.
I mean. this baby tops out
at almost 35 miles an hour.
Well. send it back.
[Neil clears throat]
The flames are a custom job.
They won't take it back.
[chuckles wryly] Can't say I blame 'em.
You know you can always
stay with us longer if you need to.
That two-bedroom
isn't big enough for the four of you.
You don't need me on the sofa as well.
Besides. I've buried every dime I've got
into this… tomb.
Gotta make sure it doesn't burn down
before I figure a way out.
Well. at least it's pretty.
- It's dry.
- It's a desert.
Exactly.
Still. I see why Mom picked it.
She never liked the Chicago winters.
Yeah. shouldn't you be
getting on the road?
Back to Albuquerque.
miss out on all that rush-hour traffic?
It's Sunday. Dad.
Yeah. weekend traffic.
Even worse.
[wistful. emotional music playing]
[Sam exhales]
- Call me if you need anything.
- Don't worry about me.
[voice cracking] See ya soon. Raccoon.
Bye-bye. Butterfly.
[engine turns over]
[woman on TV] There's always
something to do in The Boroughs.
Play 18 holes on any one
of our three award-winning golf courses.
Or keep healthy
in our brand-new fitness center
with self-regulating.
therapeutic walking pools.
[Blaine] I'm CEO Blaine Shaw.
and my grandfather founded
this little slice of heaven
way back in 1950.
The man at the top.
Keeping you healthy and happy has been
the family business for almost 75 years.
So kick back and enjoy.
I promise. you'll have
the time of your life.
[knocking at door]
[man] Hello?
Oh! Howdy. neighbor.
I'm Jack.
You know your doorknob's broken?
I'm kind of the welcome wagon
around these parts.
Care for a beer?
No. Thank you.
Oh. my dogs are barking.
I got a touch of the gout.
Doesn't help that I shot a full 18 today.
Shot an 82. which is not bad
with a ten handicap.
You play golf?
- No.
- Hey.
What's your name?
Sam Cooper.
Ah. yeah.
Well. I don't even mind
the gout so much. Sammy.
It's the sleep apnea
that tiddles my winks.
I gotta sleep in a chair
hooked up to this machine
to keep me breathing.
I feel like the Elephant Man. Yeah.
Because he could not sleep lying down.
You ever seen that movie?
Yeah. sure. It's a classic.
Mel Brooks produced it.
A fellow film buff. I see.
[Jack laughs]
Used to be in entertainment myself.
I was a weatherman. you know.
♪ KOB4 Santa Fe ♪
The problem with my sleep situation
is it makes it tricky with the ladies.
In my younger days.
I was always the big spoon. you know?
Now if I…
cuddle up. fall asleep after.
I'll die.
And that's a definite mood killer.
I imagine so.
Don't get me wrong. Sammy.
I'm not a player.
One at a time.
Every time.
That's my motto.
They banned 100 residents
for having an orgy
in the community center last month.
Can you believe it?
I get it.
Uh. that's not my thing.
I get it. though.
I'm seeing this great lady now.
Only thing is she's always rubbing
this cannabis Tiger Balm on herself.
It's arthritis.
It smells like black licorice.
She is a fine-looking woman.
Special. you know?
What's your situation?
You married? Divorced?
Widowed.
Sorry to hear it.
You know.
I don't know your emotional journey.
but single fellas like ourselves
are Wonka tickets around here.
Golden.
I appreciate you stopping by.
Jack. but it's been a long day.
Ah say no more. I can take a hint.
But before I skedoodle.
I wanted to invite you to a barbecue
in your honor over at my place.
You'll get to know the neighbors.
- How's Tuesday sound?
- Not good.
Well. you look over your schedule
and let me know. okay?
Keep the beer.
I'll just take one for the road.
The Boroughs is a good place.
We take care of each other. you know.
Like a family.
I'm full up on family.
Yeah. I got you.
Think about that barbecue.
I make a hell of a kebab.
[door closes]
[tender. emotional music playing]
Morning.
[Sam] Morning. love.
I thought I might go up to that good
farmer's market at Logan Square today.
Mmm. Yeah. I need shallots
for dinner tonight.
So come with me.
[clicks tongue]
I was gonna work on the car.
[Lilly sputters. laughs]
You and that car.
What is the point of fixing up a car
if you can't drive it?
[both chuckle]
[engine revving]
[Sam grouses]
Yeah. baby!
We got it!
[crunchy punk rock music
playing over stereo]
["Oye Cómo Va" by Santana
playing faintly in distance]
♪ Oye cómo va. mi ritmo ♪
Oh. perfect.
Who are these people?
[groovy Latin rock continuing]
I found his wife's obituary.
- Who?
- Our new neighbor.
Samuel Darwin Cooper.
Born Chicago. Illinois.
December 10. 1953.
[man] You gotta stop stalking people.
[woman] I'm not stalking.
I'm investigating.
You're not a reporter anymore.
Journalist.
And that makes it stalking.
His wife died of a stroke five months ago.
Oh. gosh. She was young.
Not even 70.
Worked for Northrop Grumman.
Thirty-five years
as an aeronautical engineer.
So we know he's smart.
"Education is not
the learning of the facts.
but the training of the mind to think."
Who said that?
Einstein.
No. maybe Mr. Peabody.
One or the other. I don't remember.
Art? I was thinking
we should go for a walk today.
Your doctors say you need exercise.
real exercise. not the bendy-bendy stuff.
I can't. I'm playing golf with Maximo.
Well. are we still on for a film tonight?
Dog Day Afternoon is playing
at The Palace.
I'm sorry. I forgot.
Loser buys dinner.
and Max always loses. so. you know…
So. hey to Maximo.
Okey dokey.
Mmm. See you later.
Yeah.
[quirky. intriguing music playing]
Oh boy.
[cart alert blaring]
[tires skidding]
No!
Fuck! Fuck!
There he is! Sam the man!
Look. I just wanted to apologize.
- I came on a little strong last night.
- Oh. I can't talk now. Jack.
Oh. sure. sure. sure. We can talk about
that whole barbecue shindig later.
There's no rush on that.
Nice wheels. by the way.
Yeah. there's nothing like an ICON.
I got a '23. I…
Now. that's a beaut!
Love the flames. hot stuff!
[tires screech]
[tour guide] Young Marcus Shaw
was working in the local coal mine
when he first imagined a town
just for retirees back in 1949.
Everyone thought he was crazy.
but at that very first open house.
the line of cars…
They featured state-of-the-art appliances.
like the brand-new Westinghouse oven.
which you can see to your left right here.
[guide laughing] Oh!
We have something special.
You guys come around.
This right here…
[receptionist] We can make that work.
Mm-hmm.
Shouldn't be a problem.
Yes.
That's right.
Thank you for calling The Boroughs.
where you'll have the time of your life.
Can I help you. sweetie?
Yeah. uh. my name's Sam Cooper.
I need to speak to Mr. Shaw.
What is this in regards to?
Getting out of my contract.
Oh. Well. that's a new one.
Unfortunately. Mr. Shaw
isn't in the office today.
Let me check his schedule.
["Thunder Road"
by Bruce Springsteen playing over PA]
[soulful. anthemic rock playing]
[heartbeat rushing]
You're in luck. I can squeeze you in
at 2:00 p.m. on Wednesday.
Do you want it?
- [heart thumping]
- [shrill. distressing music spikes. halts]
Lilly. where are the shallots I asked for?
Shit!
I forgot!
I can't cook chimichurri without shallots.
- Use onions!
- You can't be serious.
Well. they're basically the same.
I'm gonna pretend you didn't say that.
["Thunder Road"
by Bruce Springsteen playing]
♪ Hey. that's me. and I want you only ♪
- What are you doing?
- Dance with me.
I have to cook dinner.
It can wait.
- This isn't gonna work.
- Yeah?
We both know that isn't true.
Pork chops are gonna burn.
[Lilly laughs] Don't be such a grump.
♪ So you're scared. and you're thinking
That maybe we ain't that young… ♪
[Sam] ♪ …anymore ♪
[both. sweetly] ♪ Show a little faith
There's magic in the night ♪
♪ You ain't a beauty
But hey. you're all right ♪
♪ Oh. and that's all right with me ♪
[song continuing]
♪ You can hide 'neath your covers ♪
♪ And study your pain ♪
♪ Make crosses from your lovers
Throw roses in the rain ♪
[Lilly gags]
Lilly?
Lilly!
Look at me. honey! Lilly!
[receptionist]
Mr. Cooper. are you all right?
Yeah. I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
You look like you've seen a ghost.
I have to go. Sorry.
Did you want that appointment?
[bombastic. strident music playing]
Mickey Mantle!
- Nice shot.
- Sun got in my eyes.
All right. new guy.
When we get in there.
let me do the talking.
This lady's a handful.
Comprende?
[choir singing
"All These Things That I've Done"]
Looking good. everyone.
Diane? Ooh. that's nice.
Sheila. don't use your hands.
Use the pliers. okay?
Then you can get right in there.
Oh no!
No. no. no. Absolutely not.
I specifically told the Seraphim thing
to send anybody but you.
Anybody but Chief Rent-a-Slop.
What can we do. Renee?
I've been robbed. Again.
And… what are we missing this time?
A bag of rose quartz.
What's that? Expensive?
[Renee] No. it's like ten bucks.
But I know that I put them on the shelf
in the storage room last night.
and this morning. they were gone.
So somebody broke in and stole them.
Huh. Any sign of a break-in?
- No.
- Of course not.
Look. nothing we can do.
We could file a report.
Yes. yes. Thank you…
- Paz.
- Thank you. Paz.
Let's do that. Let's take a report.
You know. last week.
Meredith Stidwell reported her car stolen.
Turns out… she loaned it
to her daughter and forgot.
It just happens all the time
in folks your age.
You know. look around.
I mean. you got stones worth
a lot more than ten bucks here.
You misplaced your quartz and forgot it.
Just like Meredith Stidwell.
and just like the last time you called.
The worst thing I could do for you
is file a report that says.
"Confused old woman is confused again."
You're welcome.
[moody. enigmatic music playing]
- [man 1] What do you call it?
- [man 2] Brentwood.
What do you do here nights?
They eat their dinner.
They all come here and eat the big dinner.
[man 1]
You're a pretty bright boy. aren't you?
Well--
[mysterious music playing]
[music trails off]
[car backfiring loudly]
Jesus!
- [car backfires]
- [grumbles]
[engine grinding]
Stop!
- What?
- Just stop.
Just give me a damn minute.
You a mechanic?
Engineer.
Ah. Close enough.
I'm Renee.
Sam.
- New guy on the block.
- I guess.
Try the engine.
- Just like that?
- Just like that.
Huh. All right.
[engine turns over smoothly]
Whoa! Thank you.
Hey!
Hey! I'm trying to thank you!
I don't want it. I just want some sleep.
Well then. say you're welcome.
Excuse me?
Here's a tip.
When somebody says "thank you."
you just say "you're welcome"
instead of being a snippy little bitch.
The other person will go on their way.
and you can go back to doing
what all grumpy old men love to do.
Be alone.
You're welcome.
Attaboy. Sam.
[rowdy punk rock playing on radio]
[faint tapping]
[tapping continuing]
[suspenseful music playing]
Who the hell are you?
Oh. shit.
Where's Grace?
Uh. take it easy. buddy.
It's in the walls.
- What is?
- The owl.
Owl?
This is all wrong. Where's Grace?
Oh. wait. Wait. wait. wait.
Grace. She used to live here?
You're her husband? I can help you.
No. I have to find the door.
We can find the door together.
Um. just put the knife down.
You're one of them.
Where's Grace?
You took her! Where is she?
You've got her! You give her back!
- Give her back. dammit!
- Stop it!
- Give her back!
- I don't have her. you psycho!
Give her back!
[Sam] Help. somebody!
Somebody. help!
Help!
Calm down!
[orderly] Edward. that's enough!
No. no. no. He's one of them.
- [orderly] Time to go home.
- But this is my home.
[Edward] No! Gracie!
All patched up.
Lucky you didn't need stitches.
Yeah. that's me. Mr. Lucky.
- How we doing over here?
- He is good as new.
- [security guard laughs]
- I wouldn't go that far.
[guard] Well. I realize
you had a rough morning.
Don't want to take up your time.
But you need anything. call security.
you ask for Hank. I'll get you sorted.
What about the police?
Well. legally speaking.
The Boroughs isn't a town.
It's all unincorporated land.
They set it up that way so the company
doesn't have to provide schools
or… police departments.
Now. there's a county sheriff.
but those boys are stretched pretty thin.
so we try not to sweat 'em
with the small stuff.
Small stuff? A man broke into my house.
- I'm sorry.
- I was attacked.
- I understand.
- Apparently. you do not understand.
Maybe the sheriff will.
Look. Mr. Cooper. no one is gonna stop you
from calling the sheriff
if you're dead set on it.
But there's someone
you should talk to first.
- Who's that?
- My boss.
Blaine Shaw.
Fine. But I call shotgun.
Can't allow that. Sorry.
[suspenseful music playing]
- I thought I was meeting the boss.
- You are.
- [Sam] What is this place?
- The Manor.
It's where they stick the potatoes.
Like your little visitor today.
- Some door.
- We take security seriously here.
Yeah? How'd the guy
who attacked me get out?
We're still figuring that out.
But I assure you. it won't happen again.
[placid. tranquil music playing]
[Paz] Apparently. all this helps
folks suffering from dementia.
Makes them feel at home.
Kind of trippy. right?
That it is.
- Mr. Shaw's waiting for you in the café.
- Café?
We'll be out front
to take you home when you're done.
Excuse me. Do you have the time?
- It's almost 10:00.
- Oh. good.
Then I haven't missed my bus.
Mrs. Taylor? [chuckles]
There we go.
Oops. Sorry.
Hold on.
Just a second. There…
There we are.
Pretty as a picture.
Mr. Cooper.
Hello. I'm Blaine Shaw.
CEO of The Boroughs.
I know who you are. I've seen you on TV.
Of course.
Thank you for agreeing to meet with me.
Would you like a cold drink?
We have a soda machine. various juices.
No. I'm not thirsty.
Well. please have a seat.
No. I'll stand.
Thank you.
First things first.
I owe you an apology. Mr. Cooper.
It is my responsibility
to keep our residents safe.
and I failed you.
and for that. I am very sorry.
- Yeah. I don't want your apology.
- No.
You want out of your contract.
How do you know?
Well. I heard about what happened
with your transition manager
and with my receptionist.
It's my town. Mr. Cooper.
Nothing goes on around here
without my knowing. so…
I took the liberty
of speaking with financing.
Had the proper documents drawn up.
Provided I don't call the sheriff.
That's right.
Yeah. fine with me.
There is. uh. one more thing.
What?
Edward would like to apologize.
Edward?
Don't worry. He's properly medicated.
He's no harm to anyone. I can assure you.
Yeah. I'll keep my distance. all the same.
Edward?
Edward? Can you hear me?
Is it time for supper?
Oh no. not yet.
but there's somebody here to see you.
Gracie?
No. no. It's. um… It's Mr. Cooper.
Do you remember what we talked about?
About Mr. Cooper?
Oh. yes. Yes.
Mr. Cooper…
I'm sorry. Mr. Cooper.
I am sorry.
Hmm?
Well done. Edward.
[Sam] What's wrong with him? Alzheimer's?
Maxwell's.
It's a rare neurological disease.
It causes the brain
to literally wither and die.
There's no cure. no treatment.
Edward and the world are locked in a race
to see who can forget the other first.
What about friends. family?
Edward and Grace had a son. Joey.
but sadly. he passed quite young.
No. The Manor is all Edward has now.
Like everyone here.
Well. I think we have taken up
quite enough of your time. Mr. Cooper.
You are on to bigger and better things.
So here's your contract.
All that's left for you to do is sign.
Of course.
you could always stay.
Now. I… I realize it's a long shot.
We haven't exactly
put our best foot forward. but…
well. I know what you've lost. Sam.
And I suspect
you don't have anywhere to go.
Do you?
You know. loneliness is a disease
just as savage as Maxwell's.
And far more common these days.
But nobody's ever alone in The Boroughs.
Well. um…
Maybe I'll just have a lawyer look at it
before I sign.
Well. that's very wise. Mr. Cooper.
You take your time.
Not too much. though.
As my wife likes to remind me.
time is a precious commodity around here.
[intriguing. mysterious music playing]
[music trailing off]
Sam the man.
[Jack chuckles]
Everything hunky-dory?
I saw the wambulances
in front of your place today.
- Got me worried.
- Oh. all good. False alarm.
Oh. glad to hear. Yeah.
Yeah. I… I just stopped by because…
Well. you know.
I was thinking about that barbecue.
- Oh. yeah?
- Yeah.
Thinking anything in particular?
Yeah. I was thinking. you know. maybe…
it's not such a bad idea.
You know. maybe I should. uh…
Yeah. maybe I should meet the neighbors.
Makes sense.
- How's Thursday?
- No good. no.
Uh. Friday would work.
I'll make a few calls.
Yeah.
[serene music playing]
[phone ringing]
- Hey. Claire Bear.
- [Claire] Hey.
I have a favor to ask.
Do you have Mom's vinyl
of Born to Run? I was like Ella's age--
Yeah.
I can't really talk now.
The neighbor's throwing me a barbecue.
- [shocked laugh] And you're going?
- Well. you don't have to sound so shocked.
No. I'm not at all surprised
by your sudden popularity.
Yeah. All right. all right.
Bye-bye. Butterfly.
See you soon. Raccoon.
And don't forget about Bruce.
- What?
- Mom's record.
All right. I'll find it.
Gotta go.
I have stage-four prostate cancer.
Oh.
I probably don't have much time left.
It seems a waste
to spend it standing outside a party.
Not that I'd call six people
in a backyard much of a party.
but sadly. it's as close as I get
since they banned me
from the community center.
Cowards.
I'm Sam.
Wally.
- You gonna stand out here all night. Sam?
- I'm not very good at parties.
My wife was the sociable one.
People only liked me when I was with her.
Well. I'm beloved.
So stick close.
["Shining Star"
by Earth. Wind & Fire playing]
And that's the part
people don't want to talk about.
The documents.
You can make fun of them
hillbillies seeing swamp gas all you want.
but then you've got to explain
Nathan Twining's 1947 memo. right?
Absolutely. Art.
Absolutely.
Look who I found loitering out front.
There he is.
Sam the man.
- Good to see you.
- I brought some beer.
That's great. That's great.
Let me introduce you to the gang here.
- We got Art and Judy here.
- How's it going?
- They live next door to you.
- Here. I'll take this.
And you come to me if you need anything.
Because I have my finger
on the pulse of this place here.
What pulse?
Oh. Wally. You obviously met him.
- And the mighty Renee.
- Yeah. we met.
That's fantastic. All right.
Well. let's all get down to business.
Go in there. grab your plates.
Just because Carlos Castaneda lied
about everything that he did
doesn't mean what he meant--
So. Jack. which lucky widow
are you sending
into peaks of ecstasy this week?
Whoo! Careful. Wally.
We both know you're the only man
in The Boroughs
with a higher body count than mine.
What? He's damn right.
By the way.
I was monogamous 15 years after 9/11. so…
I hate that term. "body count."
[Jack] You're right.
What would you call it?
My "back catalogue."
- That's good. I like that.
- [Renee] Right? It's better. Yeah.
How are you settling in?
Oh. fine.
Couple of bumps.
Did you know Grace and Edward?
Yeah.
Grace and I used to play tennis together.
She was a hoot.
What about Edward?
Edward?
He was a dick.
It's about bringing people together.
[overlapping laughter]
[Art] This is Blue Dream.
A hybrid sativa.
Tastes like sweet berries.
[Renee] No. no. no. I'll pass.
You still on the vape?
It's healthier.
Ah-ha-ha!
I tried weed salsa the other day.
Unnecessary.
They put weed in everything now.
I have weed Tiger Balm for arthritis.
It smells of licorice.
Some people hate the aroma. but I love it.
Oh no. I don't think I'd better do that.
I'm going in for surgery tomorrow.
[Renee] Oh. Jack. Is it the gout?
Are you gonna have a toe removed?
[Jack] No. no. no.
I'm having a mole cut off.
[Renee] What? Come on.
Getting a mole sliced off does not count.
- [Jack] It counts.
- No.
No. I'm a retired doctor.
It doesn't count.
I had my spine fused.
Now. that is surgery. Here. here.
- Look at this.
- He's gonna show.
[Art] Yeah. take a look at this.
There it is.
All right. You know what?
That ain't nothing. Sorry.
I had a whole new hip installed.
- Right?
- Amazing.
Okay. y'all gonna have to imagine
my C-section scar.
Aw. where's the fun in that?
Show us what you're working with. playboy.
All my scars are emotional.
I'm afraid to say
I think I got you all beat.
Check it out.
God. they cracked your chest.
They went in twice.
Ladies and gentlemen. we have a winner!
- [whooping]
- [Jack] Just saying.
How about you. new guy?
You got any battle scars?
My retina detached.
Your retina detached?
Yeah.
Like in a bar fight?
No. I woke up one morning.
I couldn't see out of my left eye.
Apparently. it's genetic.
Happened to my dad
when he was about the same age.
[grumbles] We all become our fathers.
The worst thing. they took my license.
Elders should be respected and venerated.
They treat us like…
- Yeah. like children.
- Yes.
- We should start a revolution.
- Yeah.
- To the Grey Rebellion!
[Art] To the Grey Rebellion!
[Jack] The Grey Rebellion!
[dark. sinister music playing]
[echoing] Lilly!
Look at me! Look at me!
Help!
- Somebody help!
- [heart beating]
Judy!
- Judy. Hold on! Judy!
- [Art] Shit!
- You have to hold her from behind.
- [Jack] You're gonna be okay.
Hold on. I'll get her a glass of water.
- [Judy gagging]
- [Jack] Good. good.
[Art] It's all right. I got her.
- You sure?
- Come on. baby. You all right?
- [Renee] Thank God.
- [Art] Come on. Sit down.
Sit down.
There you go. All right. babe.
[music trailing off]
Fuck you! Fuck!
Fuck you! Fucking piece of shit!
Fuck.
My wife is dead.
I'm sorry. buddy.
My wife's dead.
And the world just keeps on turning.
and people just keep on
living their lives.
They shop. and they… laugh. and they eat.
And they go to sleep. and they get up.
and they do it all over again.
And I hate 'em for it!
My wife is dead.
[Sam sobs]
Yeah.
My second wife. she…
read a lot of self-help books.
Not that they helped her much. but…
that's beside the point.
I remember this one thing
that she told me once.
Grief makes your past feel too close
and your future
too far away.
Well. my wife's dead.
I don't have a future.
Yeah. but you're still here. buddy.
What. in The Boroughs?
God's waiting room?
That's what I thought once.
But the truth is.
people come here to live.
Everybody's trying to figure out
what to do with the time you got left.
And that's young people. old people.
It doesn't matter.
But here.
here. you've got not one but three
award-winning golf courses to choose from.
Golf is stupid.
That may be. but…
where else can you grab a club
and whack the shit out of something. huh?
I mean. it's a lot cheaper than…
breaking doors.
Right?
[chuckling wryly]
Well. I'll think about it.
Good enough.
[warm. gentle music playing]
Look. I gotta…
head back to the party.
make sure Judy's okay. so…
Jack.
Thank you.
Thanks for everything.
[Jack] Oh. I…
Sam the man.
[music trails off]
[operator] You've reached
Blaine Shaw at The Boroughs.
where you'll have the time of your life.
Please leave a message. and we'll get back
to you as soon as humanly possible.
[message beeps]
Mr. Shaw.
It's Sam Cooper.
Just wanted you to know
I won't be calling the sheriff.
and I don't need you
to cancel my contract.
I've decided to stay.
So I…
guess I'll see you around.
[spritely. intriguing music playing]
[music trails off]
[Sam grunts]
[faint beeping in distance]
[beeping continuing]
[low. uneasy music playing]
Jack?
Jack!
[uneasy music intensifies]
Jack?
[alert blaring]
[chilling music building]
[emotional heartland rock playing]
♪ Working on our night moves ♪
[creature rasps. shrieks]
["Night Moves" by Bob Seger playing]
[creature yowling]
♪ Mmm. sweet summertime. summertime ♪
[shrill shrieking in distance]
♪ Night moves ♪
- ♪ Night moves ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Night moves ♪
- ♪ Night moves ♪
- ♪ Sure remember the night moves ♪
[singer vocalizing]
♪ The wonder ♪
♪ Felt the lightning. yeah ♪
♪ And we waited on the thunder ♪
♪ Waited on the thunder ♪
- ♪ Night moves ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ We were working ♪
- ♪ Working and practicing ♪
- ♪ Night moves ♪
♪ Oh. for the night moves ♪
♪ Night moves ♪
- ♪ Oh. I remember ♪
- ♪ Night moves ♪
- ♪ Yeah. yeah. yeah. I remember ♪
- ♪ I remember ♪
♪ Lord. I remember ♪
[melodic vocalizing]
♪ Uh-huh. uh-huh ♪
♪ I remember. I remember ♪
[song trailing off]
[intriguing. mysterious
outro music playing]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm